

Contact information

Email

juananmgz@gmail.com

Address

- Ciudad Rodrigo, Salamanca
- Madrid

Telephone

(+34) 658 01 61 21

Nationality

Spanish

Links

- · juananmgz.com
- · linkedin.com/in/juananmgz

Competences

Social skills

Quick learning

Commitment

Agile development

Strategy

Initiative

Leadership

Organization

Performance

Responsibility

Teamwork

Languages

Spanish: Native

English: Intermediate Level

More info

Driving License

own Car

Juan Antonio Muñoz Gómez

DevOps Computer Engineer

Specialized in **Web Development & Agile Methodologies**. My goal is to offer clients the best product applying my knowledge and experience. My preferences are **Interface Design & User Experience (UI & UX)** based on **Human-Computer Interaction**.

Experience

Salamanca, Spain Feb 2021 - Jul 2021 Curricular Internships: Electronics and WebApps development

ESALab Research Group

Development of electronic devices linked to responsive lonic + React apps. Used of technologies such as 3D Design and printing, MIDI, MQTT or websockets.

Ciudad Rodrigo, **Spain** Jun 2020 - Sep 2020 Database management in business administration
 San Matías Colsuntancy

Education

Alcalá de Henares, **Spain** 2021 - Actualmente

Salamanca, **Spain** 2017 - 2021 Agile Software Web Development Univeristy of Alcalá de Henares

Computer Engineering Degree
University of Salamanca

Certificates & Courses

- · Scrum Master: Agile project management with Scrum. Viewnext (2021)
- Business and Marketing Plan. Industrial and Intellectual Property. Operations and Human Resources Plan. Fund. General USAL - Plan TCUE (2021)
- · Ionic React: Cross-Platform Mobile Development with Ionic 5. Udemy ESALab (2021)

Otras Formaciones

- English Native Language Immersion. Edinburgh (2014)
- Musical education [+16 years]. Different associations & instructors (2003-Currently)

Skills

WEB DEVELOPMENT

- P. Languages: HTML + CSS + JS/TS. Java, C#, PHP, Python, Perl ...
- Frameworks & Environments: NodeJS, Angular, React, Ionic, Bootstrap
- Containers: Docker + Kubernetes
- Servers: Nginx, Apache + PHP, Java Servlets + JSP. APIs
- Web Design: CSS/SASS + Parallax. Responsive, usability and interactivity
- Security: Routes Securization. Secure Design. Certificates
- Databases: SQL, MySQL server. ORM. Firebase
- Version Control: Git / GitHub / GitFlow

AGILE DEVELOPMENT

- Scrum + Kanban + Lean + XP: Scrum Master. Jira, Taiga, Mic. Project
- · TDD & BDD

SOME OTHER SKILLS

- · Graphic design. 3D Design and printing
- Hardware and electronics
- · Wifi y Bluetooth communication
- O. Systems, Networks and Security

Awards

- TCUE Market Oriented Prototypes Grant, Fund. General USAL (2021)
- Traditional Music Youngth Talent, Arlafolk (2019)

Articles

Listed in orcid.com: 0000-0001-6794-5445